companieshouse.gov.uk 2012-11-01

# Terms and Conditions

  * Disclaimer
  * Privacy and Cookies Statement
  * Acceptable Use Statement
  * Information collected on behalf of HMRC
  * Personal information
  * Companies House Mobile Application

**Disclaimer**

The information available on this site is not intended to be comprehensive, and many details which may be relevant to particular circumstances have been omitted. Accordingly it should not be regarded as being a complete source of company law and information, and readers are advised to seek independent professional advice before acting on anything contained herein. Companies House cannot take any responsibility for the consequences of errors or omissions. 

**Notes for Users of Company Search or Disqualified Directors Search**

The information available here is an extract from the Register of Companies / Register of Disqualified Directors which are updated on a regular basis. This may mean that occasional inaccuracies occur which we correct as soon as they are drawn to our attention. If you spot something which you think might be wrong, let us know so we can, if necessary, correct the database. 

**Company Information Supplied by Companies House**

Companies House is a registry of company information. We carry out basic checks to make sure that documents have been fully completed and signed, but we do not have the statutory power or capability to verify the accuracy of the information that companies send to us. We accept all information that companies deliver to us in good faith and place it on the public record. The fact that the information has been placed on the public record should not be taken to indicate that Companies House has verified or validated it in any way. 

When Companies House examines accounts it only make basic checks on them, for example to ensure that the appropriate documents are there, that they are for the correct financial year and that they have been signed. If, subsequently, we receive a complaint that the accounts do not comply with the Companies Acts in some way we have a duty to draw this to the company’s attention and, if appropriate, to ask for a set of revised accounts which do comply with the requirements. 

**Links to external websites**

It is our policy to obtain permission to link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or reliability of the linked websites. Listing should not be taken as endorsement of any kind. We cannot guarantee that these links will work all of the time and we have no control over the availability of linked pages.

back to top

**Privacy and Cookies**

Our cookie policy

**Information collected on behalf of HMRC**

Companies House through the Joint Registration Service will act as agents for HMRC and provide an optional service whereby when a person registers a new company, a facility will be offered so that person can also register the company for Corporation Tax.  Once incorporation at Companies House has been accepted the Corporation Tax information will be sent to HMRC and will not be retained by Companies House.

**Personal information**

The Companies House Executive Agency website does not store or capture personal information, but merely logs the user's IP address (Internet Protocol: standard allowing data to be transmitted between two devices) which is automatically recognised by the web server. 

If you register to receive updates, or order or purchase materials, your information will be held on a secure server and the data will not be shared with any organisations outside Government. It will be used only to provide you with any electronic products you have ordered, email updates on the topics you have requested, or postal information if you request that service. If you respond online to a consultation exercise your data will only be used to facilitate the analysis of responses. 

This privacy statement only covers our website at www.companieshouse.gov.uk and sub-sites of this domain. This privacy statement does not cover other websites linked to from this domain.

Companies House Executive Agency may use information it holds to prevent and detect fraud. We may also share such information, for the same purpose, with other organisations that handle public funds. 

If you have any queries please contact the Companies House Contact Centre on +44 (0)303 1234 500 or email [enquiries@companies-house.gov.uk](mailto:enquiries@companies-house.gov.uk)

back to top

**Acceptable use of Companies House Searchable Databases**

The Companies House searchable databases are designed to meet the needs of a wide range of users wishing to interrogate our information on-line. 

Due to limitations of equipment and bandwidth, they are not intended to be a source for bulk downloads. 

Individuals, companies, IP addresses or blocks of IP addresses who deny or degrade service to other users by generating unusually high numbers of daily database accesses, whether generated manually or in an automated fashion, may be denied access to these services without notice.

**Companies House Mobile Application**

Companies House Mobile Application

back to top
